Do you remember the first time you kissed me
你还记得第一次吻我吗？
Yeah
记得。
In the sewer pipe not filled with sewage
在那根没有污水的下水管道里——
It was still above ground
嗯。
I don't know if you were really serious about that kiss
我不知道你当时亲我是不是认真的，
As much as you just wanted to tell your friends
还是只想去跟朋友炫耀。
But i never kissed in t okay , good
但我从没在那之前亲过别人，所以……好吧。
Why did you
为什么要亲？
Well , i told my mother that i kissed you
嗯，我告诉了我妈，
i said i think i'm going to marry him
我说，我觉得我要嫁给他了。
And i was twelve years old
那时我十二岁。
Well , it's okay to make a big mistake like that
嗯，犯这种大错误也是可以的。
Yes , poor judgment
是的，当时判断失误。
But i remember when you gave me that wonderful birthday present
不过我记得你送给我那个精美的生日礼物，
it was a beautifully rap box
是一个包装精美的盒子，
And i was very excited because we had had the kiss
我非常兴奋，因为我们已经亲过了，
And i thought this was like really progressing
我以为事情在进展。
And i unwrapped it carefully and opened the box
我小心翼翼地拆开包装，打开了盒子，
And there in the box was the snake that was wriggling and scared the hell out of me
里面是一条蠕动的蛇，把我吓得魂飞魄散。
And it may have been one of my snakes out
而且那可能是我的一条蛇，
I get rid of because it bit my little brother
因为它咬了我弟弟，我才把它处理掉的。
Oh , so why not give it to you soon to be girlfriend
哦，那为什么不送给你快要成为女友的人呢？
Yeah
哈。
Another wonderful gift you gave me
另一次你送的礼物也很妙，
You came up to me very serious
你一本正经地走过来，
And perhaps to give me a kiss
像是要给我一个吻，
And then you took a bunch of eggs and smash them on my head
然后把一堆鸡蛋打碎砸在我头上。
I had these disgusting eggs dripping down my face
那些恶心的蛋液顺着我脸往下流，
I must have looked like an omelet
我肯定看起来像一个煎蛋卷。
But i stayed with you anyway . you did
但我还是没有离开你。你确实没有。
I think once i decided that you were gonna be my boyfriend
我想，一旦我决定你就是我男友，
Whether you liked it or not
不管你愿意不愿意，
I was gonna persist
我就会一直坚持。
I did those stupid things to you
我做那些傻事，
Because you're the prettiest girl in the neighborhood
是因为你是我们街上最漂亮的女孩，
But a lot of other boys were interested in you
很多男孩都对你有意思，
So how do you stand out
我要怎么才能脱颖而出？
And those things may have been obnoxious
那些事也许很讨厌，
But i would always forgive you
但我总是原谅你，
Because despite all the mean things you might have done to me
因为在我心里，尽管你做了那些坏事，
In my mind , those were always acts of love
那些在我看来都是爱的表现。
So it worked
所以有效果。
It did work
确实有效果。
And the good news is you grew out of that face
好消息是你后来长大成熟了。
I mean , by high school , things change quite a bit
高中以后，事情就完全不一样了。
The sixties were difficult years
六十年代是很动荡的年月，
Nonstop chaos
混乱不断，
Nonstop war
战争不停，
And you and i realized that we could be each other's anchor
我们两个意识到，彼此可以成为对方的锚。
Yeah , even though you were still a little nuts
是的，哪怕你那时候还是有点疯。
But i don't know if i could have had that with anybody else
但我觉得我无法和别人建立这样的关系，
I think that's why you're so special
这就是你为什么那么特别。
And your ability to make others feel loved it's pretty special
你让别人感受到爱的能力，非常了不起。
Thanks
谢谢你。
Thanks for always supporting me
谢谢你一直支持我。
Of course
当然了。
With a snake in an egg
用蛇和鸡蛋的方式。
Ha ha
哈哈。